Suddenly Explorers! Ikinari Expedition!
Please take care of the two members of Uji's secret record and the ikinari talkers!
Please take care of us! We are the ikinari expeditionary group!
Today we have Mr. Yasumori and Ms. Karen!
There's a little reason why I invited them today.
What? What?
It's nothing like that.
I'm sorry I didn't do it. I just jumped out.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I know! I know! You got it?
I threw 100 bowling balls. You've never done that before.
There's a reason we called you here... for a project we're working on today.
Let's try our hand at announcing the closing of the museum.
Yay!
Here you go.
This has become a tradition.
I'd like to challenge each and every one of you.
to announce the closing of e-BINS
to announce the closing of e-BINS.
Each of you has done it once.
Two of you have not done it yet.
That's right.
I called them today.
They called me up.
Soon today.
E-Beans will be closing soon.
So I've asked them to come up with an original announcement.
I've asked the two of you to come up with something original, and you'll announce it.
I've never heard of announcing a cover, but it's okay if you don't want to.
I don't have to make an announcement, but as long as you both express your individuality, I'm sure whatever you say will be fine.
I'd like to thank all of you for choosing me.
I'd like to send my sincere thanks to all of you who have chosen and wanted our products.
I'd like to deliver it with all my heart, and I'm sure it'll be a mess.
You're pretending to be a mess after this, aren't you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm an adult.
That's for sure.
I want to announce it in an adult manner.
If we go too far, we might get in trouble if we receive complaints.
I'll have the two of you do the announcements with that in mind.
Okay, then, let's move to the information area.
Let's move on to the information area.
Okay, let's move to the information area.
Let's go.
Let's go to the information desk.
What are you doing here? We all took the elevator.
We just got here. The information desk is closed.
It's closing.
That's sad.
We do this every day, so don't worry about it.
No, no, no, we do it every day.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
How are you today? I'm doing great today.
My goal is to be great every day this year.
What's that?
Then let's have a little bit of haikernance.
The top performer is Mr. Yasumori.
I'm a very strong announcer.
I was a broadcaster in elementary and middle school, so I'm used to it.
That's right.
I'm used to having my voice heard inside the ship through a microphone.
I'm quite used to it.
Then you can leave it to me.
I can leave it to you.
Yes, very kind of you.
Polite?
Yes, I'd like to go.
I'd like to go at my own time, so please look forward to it.
You can do it in your own timing.
Yes, I will be there. Some people may fall in love with your voice, so I hope you can make it float with your cute voice.
Now then, let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen! Thank you very much for visiting e-BEANS today!
Yay!
On the 10th, at 20:00
the museum will be closed.
What?
Do you still want to stay here?
I don't know how you feel.
All right, kids.
Let's get out of here as soon as possible.
I made a promise to your sister.
And now...
My purchases today
Schemas, lips...
A blonde wig.
E-bean's is
It's gal-friendly.
What did you guys buy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bought clothes and took purikura
Played with puri kura.
We went to a fancy cafe and had tea.
That's so cool!
It's so nice!
It's been too nice a day for the gals
I got a good deal today
Tomorrow will be another great day for sure!
I hope you all have a great tax day
All the gals are waiting for you!
That's all for now, from suddenly Tohoku-san
This is suddenly Mr. Tohoku's Waka Yasumori!
I'm embarrassed to say that I'm not polite at all, but I'm just a gal!
Did I come off as a gal?
I knew you would do it...
You were being polite.
I guess so.
As a representative of the gals...
I closed the show.
But... as a former member of the broadcasting club...
I'm proud of you.
You didn't seem nervous.
No, maybe a little... but inwardly...
I was wondering if I could handle it.
But it was good. It was a good experience.
What did you think of it?
I know, right?
I hope you weren't offended.
You don't think it's okay?
No, it's fine.
You said something about false eyelashes.
That's right.
Stick with it and win!
That's what you want to happen to people.
It's nice to see your personality.
Thank you.
You're the gal who did it.
Okay, Karen, let's go next.
You got it.
And now we have Ms. Cullen.
What do you think? Enthusiasm.
Everyone had their own personality.
I, as an idol
I felt like an E-BEANS
Be the E-BEANS!
As the E-BEANS?
Yes, that's right.
E-BEANS, you're an idol.
I think of myself as an idol.
I'll do my best.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what you're talking about, but I'm nervous when the leader says something like this.
Then let's get there in time.
What is it now?
I'm just saying, I'll do my best.
"Speak up"? Yes, that's right.
Like before a live performance. It's important.
Who was that?
It's the coward.
Hoshikinzoku?
Hoshikinzoku? Hoshikinzoku?
Okay, I'll go.
Welcome to e-means!
We're closing e-means in a few days.
Oh, I just got here.
Me too.
Did everyone have fun today?
I'm sure there are many more who could have enjoyed themselves even more.
You all go through a lot of hardships just by being alive.
Work, school, study, housework, child-rearing
Work, school, study, housework, parenting, and many other things.
We at eavins are here for you.
We at Evins want to make you smile as much as possible.
We want to make you smile as much as possible.
Because Eavins is a building
We can't fly by your side when you're having a hard time.
We can't fly by your side when you're having a hard time, but we're always waiting for you,
We'll be waiting for you at all times, so please come see us again anytime.
Everything in eBeans is for you.
We have the cutest clothes for you,
There are the cutest clothes for you, the most delicious food for you, and it's up to you which one you pick up.
Take everything you like and be very happy!
We wish you happiness!
We may not be able to make a big deal out of it
But the magic that makes you smile
I'm sure I'll be able to make you smile
I'm sure I'll have a few of them
We look forward to seeing you again
If it's nice to meet you today
I'm sure there are some of you who always come to see me
Some of you are here just because I met you today, and some of you are here all the time.
I want you to be happy now that we've met today.
So, I know there's not much time left, but today, today...
I want you to enjoy this time that we have here at Ebbie's... this time that I get to spend with you... in a way that you can't possibly imagine.
I hope you enjoy it in your own unique way!
Okay, I'm going to make my last sound!
I hope you'll follow my lead!
Eavins is the best!
This is Karen Tachibana from Suddenly Talk! My hands are shaking ... I've been an idol all my life and this is all I know, so I thought I'd share this with you guys.
I have not been an idol all my life.
But you were so sweet.
I didn't understand what you meant.
E-WINGS is a building.
You can't fly away from it, but...
That's right.
When you're going through a hard time...
I want to fly away.
In fact, E-WINGS is also
I was nervous.
Long and safe
It was the longest time in history, you know.
It's amazing. What happens when you close the doors so precariously?
Certainly. Certainly.
It's so interesting. It was safe.
Well, I was disappointed that I couldn't speak up at the end.
Evins is the best. That's right.
I've been practicing this one, taking the last chime sound for the piano.
I wanted to play this chime after I played "Evinuz is the Best," but my pitch was not so good.
But my pitch wasn't very good, so I don't think it came across well.
It's a shame.
I see what you mean... the sound of information.
That's right.
It didn't work.
Let's try one more time.
One more time.
No, not again.
He's not that bad.
I'm a little disappointed... but let him have the best part once... just to hear his voice...
Yes...
There he is!
He's not for sale.
The one you often see in the back before a concert...
Let's go to the back of the stage, the kind of thing you often see in the backstage area before a live performance.
I'll just decide here and be done with it.
I'll do my best to put my heart and soul into it.
I'll do my best with all my heart.
What? I told you to do it, but now...
I'm sorry, but the announcer's turned off.
I'm sorry, but it's not going to be played in the museum.
But may I hear it live? Last one.
Here we go.
The Evin Vortex is the best.
Thank you very much.
And so...
Closing announcements are over.
How was it, Mr. Yasumura?
Yes, I think so.
In terms of feelings...
I feel like I was in elementary and junior high school.
I was like a kid in elementary and junior high school
I felt like I was in elementary and junior high school.
But I wasn't that nervous.
It was great.
You did it.
You looked great.
You were good.
No, I wasn't.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
I'm just glad we finally got to do something that's become a tradition.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
It was great.
How was it for you, Karen?
Well, it was a very exciting experience,
Yeah, it was.
Well, I wanted to share it with Evin, who has been very kind to me, and with everyone who came,
I wanted to share it with Evin, who has been so kind to me, and with everyone who came to the show,
No, no, no. Where do you want to convey that?
Where do you want to convey it?
You would normally do that at a live performance, wouldn't you?
Well, I would like to take this opportunity,
I was very happy to be able to deliver it to you through my way of thinking. Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo...
Boo boo boo...that was quite a long speech!
Is there a phrase you wanted to convey the most?
I can't go to your wives because I'm not a good rider, but I'll always be waiting for you to come back.
I'm just saying that I have a place for you.
I can't believe you could say such a nice thing about me.
Sushi rocks.
I'm used to live music.
Not a recording? Every day.
Live?
I want to put my heart and soul into it.
I think you two were great.
It was great.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure we'll do it again in some other way.
You know, information.
Any variation.
The possibilities are endless.
Wouldn't it be nice to read a regular text?
I'd like to do that.
It might make you nervous, though.
I have to make mistakes.
If you make a mistake, it's not good.
That's great.
That's all for today's exploration.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
eBee's is the best!
Bye.